Guide to the Salo W. Baron Papers, 1900-1980
Department of Special Collections
- Series 8. Manuscript Series (Other authors), 18.5 linear ft. (37 boxes)
  - Jewish Social Studies; Index (Box 678, Folder 25)
  - misc. photocopies (Box 679, Folder 1)
  - The Americas, vol. XXVIII, Oct. 1971, no. 2; galleys (Box 679, Folder 2)
  - Peter R. Frank, The German Area Collection, photocopy (Box 679, Folder 3)
  - Peter R. Frank, Narrative on a Good Meal; photocopy (Box 679, Folder 4)
  - Interview with Rabbi Marshall T. Meyer in: Nueva Presencia (1982); photocopy (Box 679, Folder 5)
  - Nathan Galzer, publications; photocopies (Box 679, Folder 6)
  - G. Nahon, Demogrpahie des juifs portugais à Saint-Esprit-les-Bayonne (1751-87); photocopy (Box 679, Folder 7)
  - S. Kaplan; publications; photocopies (Box 679, Folder 8)
  - My World As A Jew; Memoirs by Israel Goldstein (1984); photocopies (Box 679, Folder 9)
  - My World As A Jew; Memoirs by Israel Goldstein (1984); photocopies (Box 679, Folder 10)
  - My World As A Jew; Memoirs by Israel Goldstein (1984); photocopies (Box 679, Folder 11)
  - S. Grayzel, Reference to the Jews (1950-51); photocopy (Box 679, Folder 12)
  - Book review of Israel Schenker's Coat of Many Colors (1985) (Box 679, Folder 13)
  - M. L. Diamond, Martin Buber Jewish Existentialist (Box 679, Folder 14)
  - Reuben Ainsztein, Jewish Resistance in Nazi-Occupied Eastern Europe; galleys (Box 680, Folder 1)
  - Reuben Ainsztein, Jewish Resistance in Nazi-Occupied Eastern Europe; galleys (Box 680, Folder 2)
  - Reuben Ainsztein, Jewish Resistance in Nazi-Occupied Eastern Europe; galleys (Box 680, Folder 3)
  - Reuben Ainsztein, Jewish Resistance in Nazi-Occupied Eastern Europe; galleys (Box 680, Folder 4)
  - Reuben Ainsztein, Jewish Resistance in Nazi-Occupied Eastern Europe; galleys (Box 680, Folder 5)
  - Rufus Learsi, The Jews in America: A History (1954); galleys (Box 681, Folder 1)
  - Fragments of galleys (Box 681, Folder 2)
  - Stuart L. Charmé, From Maoism to the Talmud, galleys (Box 681, Folder 3)
  - photocopies, no author, no title (Box 681, Folder 4)
  - Oscar Handlin, Adventure in Freedom; galleys (Box 681, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewish Affairs; (1980-85); galleys (Box 681, Folder 6)
  - Ivo Lapenna, Developments in Soviet Domestic Legislation (1985); fragments; photocopies(1985) (Box 681, Folder 7)
  - Eli Ginzberg, Keeper of the Law: Louis Ginzberg (1966); galleys(1966) (Box 681, Folder 8)
  - A. Altman, Moses Mendelsohn (1973); gallyes(1973) (Box 682, Folder 1)
  - A. Altman, Moses Mendelsohn (1973); gallyes(1973) (Box 682, Folder 2)
  - A. Altman, Moses Mendelsohn (1973); gallyes(1973) (Box 682, Folder 3)
  - A. Altman, Moses Mendelsohn (1973); gallyes(1973) (Box 682, Folder 4)
  - A. Altman, Moses Mendelsohn (1973); gallyes(1973) (Box 682, Folder 5)
  - Benjamin Nelson, Scholastic Rationale of "Conscience;" photocopies (Box 682, Folder 6)
  - Benjamin Nelson, Conscience and the Making of Early Modern Cultures; photocopies (Box 682, Folder 7)
  - Bibliographical Information; photocopies (Box 682, Folder 8)
  - E. Kedourie, Islam Today; photocopy (Box 682, Folder 9)
  - Uriah Zevi Englemann, The Rise of the Jew in the Western World (1940); galleys (Box 682, Folder 10)
  - Lawrence V. Berman, various publications; photocopies (Box 682, Folder 11)
  - Invitations to Jewish Services; photocopies (Box 682, Folder 12)
  - Gerson D. Cohen, ed., The Book of Tradition by Abraham Ibn Daud; galleys (Box 683, Folder 1)
  - Gerson D. Cohen, ed., The Book of Tradition by Abraham Ibn Daud; galleys (Box 683, Folder 2)
  - Gerson D. Cohen, ed., The Book of Tradition by Abraham Ibn Daud; galleys (Box 683, Folder 3)
  - L. S. Dawidowicz, The Golden Tradition (1967); bound galleys(1967) (Box 683, Folder 4)
  - Text in Hebrew; galleys (Box 683, Folder 5)
  - galleys; no title, no author (Box 684, Folder 1)
  - galleys; no title, no author (Box 684, Folder 2)
  - galleys; no title, no author (Box 684, Folder 3)
  - Trial and Error; galleys (Box 684, Folder 4)
  - Trial and Error; galleys (Box 684, Folder 5)
  - P. R. Magocsi, Galicia: A Historical Survey (1983); galleys(1983) (Box 684, Folder 6)
  - galleys; no title, no author (Box 684, Folder 7)
  - Isaac Lewin, The Jewish Community in Poland (1984); galleys(1984) (Box 685, Folder 1)
  - An den hohen Constituierenden Reichstag; photocopy of document (Box 685, Folder 2)
  - Text in Hebrew; galleys (Box 685, Folder 3)
  - Emancipation and Counter-Emancipation; galleys (Box 685, Folder 4)
  - Dagobert D. Runes, Spinoza Dictionary; galleys (Box 685, Folder 5)
  - Steeled By Adversity, Index; galleys (Box 685, Folder 6)
  - Cornerstones of Religious Freedom in America (1949, 64)(1949, 64) (Box 685, Folder 7)
  - Ben Halpern, The Idea of the Jewish State (1961); galleys(1961) (Box 685, Folder 8)
  - O. Schmelz, The Israel Population Census of 1961 as a Source of Demographic Data on the Jews in the Diaspora (1966); photocopy(1966) (Box 685, Folder 9)
  - Population; Encyclopedia entry (Box 685, Folder 10)
  - Miscellanea (Box 685, Folder 11)
  - Article in Hebrew; photocopy (Box 685, Folder 12)
- Series 9. Notes, 4 linear ft. (8 boxes)
  This series consists of mostly handwritten, miscellaneous notes by Salo Wittmayer Baron; only a few of these manuscript fragments could be identified; for example, the boxes no. 686 and 687 contain, among other things, handwritten notes to A Social and Religious History of the Jews. The papers grouped together as "Miscellaneous Notes" are unidentified items the original order of which had been preserved. Some of those notes are in Hebrew Language.
  - Agendas/Diaries (Box 686, Folder 1)
  - Agendas/Diaries (Box 686, Folder 2)
  - Economics 129-130; outline of course (Box 686, Folder 3)
  - Translation of Zohar (Box 686, Folder 4)
  - A Social and Religious History of the Jews; chapter XLVI; notes 1-17; original ms; pp. 847-861; notes 1-17; first carbon; pp. 1037-1053 (Box 686, Folder 5)
  - American Jewish Historical Society; Miscellanea (Box 686, Folder 7)
  - Memorandum; Modern Jewish History (Box 686, Folder 8)
  - Gradebook; History A; 1968-69 (Box 686, Folder 9)
  - SRHJ; notebooks (Box 687, Folder 1)
  - SRHJ; notebooks (Box 687, Folder 2)
  - SRHJ?; notes (Box 687, Folder 3)
  - SRHJ?; notes (Box 687, Folder 4)
  - Modern Nationalism and Religion; notes (Box 687, Folder 5)
  - SRJH?; notes (Box 687, Folder 6)
  - SRJH?; notes (Box 687, Folder 7)
  - SRJH?; notes (Box 687, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 688, Folder 17)
  - Notes in Hebrew Language (Box 689, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 689, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 690, Folder 111)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 691, Folder 110)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 692, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 693, Folder 16)
- Series 10. Photo Series, Photo; 5.5 linear ft. (11 boxes)
  The photos are largely of Baron and his family. There are a few pictures of contemporary historical events, probably collected for Baron's own research. The materials are in a prelimiary order, but no overview has been drawn up yet.
  - Salo Baron passport photos (photos 1-15) (Box 694, Folder 1)
  - early photo of Baron (framed photo 16) (Box 694, Folder 2)
  - image of Baron (metal/woodblock 17) (Box 694, Folder 3)
  - early Baron, 1913-1920's (photos 18-32) (Box 694, Folder 4)
  - early Baron (photos 33-47) (Box 694, Folder 5)
  - Salo Baron, 1952 (photo 48) (Box 694, Folder 6)
  - publicity photos of Baron (photos 49-69) (Box 694, Folder 7)
  - photos taken of Baron while in South Africa (photos 70-80) (Box 694, Folder 8)
  - publicity photos and biographical data (photos 81-83) (Box 694, Folder 9)
  - publicity photos with negative (photos 84-96) (Box 694, Folder 10)
  - Salo Baron, 1978-1989 (photos 97-115) (Box 694, Folder 11)
  - miscellaneous family and friends, 1910-1920's (photos 116-142) (Box 694, Folder 12)
  - miscellaneous family and friends, 1910-1920's (photos 143-164) (Box 694, Folder 13)
  - miscellaneous family and friends, 1910-1920's (photos 165-184) (Box 694, Folder 14)
  - photos of Salo and Jeannette Baron,photos of friends and family (photos 185-194) (Box 694, Folder 15)
  - photos of Baron, photos of friends in Europe, photo of an infant (photos 195-203) (Box 694, Folder 16)
  - miscellaneous negatives (Box 695, Folder 1)
  - family and friends, 1920-1950's (photos 1-32) (Box 695, Folder 2)
  - family and friends, 1940's-1950's (photos 33-72) (Box 695, Folder 3)
  - 1951 photograph of Los Angeles friends along with piece of cardboard with the names of the people in the photo (photo 73) (Box 695, Folder 4)
  - miscellaneous family and friends, 1960's-1980's (photos 74-100) (Box 695, Folder 5)
  - the Hirsh wedding, 1965 (photos 101-103, with accompanying note) (Box 695, Folder 6)
  - Horowitz-Kaplan wedding, 1947 (photos 104-109) (Box 695, Folder 7)
  - Yocheved Sussman 1951 visit (photos 110-115) (Box 695, Folder 8)
  - travels (photos 116-138) (Box 695, Folder 9)
  - outdoor speech, 1953 (photos 139-168) (Box 695, Folder 10)
  - photos of Ela and Tair; the Stark-Eylangrandnieces, also photos from Ela Eylan's wedding (photos 169-193) (Box 695, Folder 11)
  - family and friends at Salo's 80th birthday gathering, 1975 (photos 194-211, with a birthday card from granddaughter Betsy) (Box 695, Folder 12)
  - family and friends at 50th wedding anniversary party, 6/12/84 (photos 212-232) (Box 695, Folder 13)
  - family and friends at 50th wedding anniversary party, 6/12/84 (photos 233-251) (Box 695, Folder 14)
  - miscellaneous family and friends (photos 252-256) (Box 695, Folder 15)
  - Early Baron family (photos 257-270) (Box 695, Folder 16)
  - Tina Katz Meisel (photos 271-284) (Box 695, Folder 17)
  - Joseph Meisel (photos 285-293) (Box 695, Folder 18)
  - Esther Katz (photos 294-286) (Box 695, Folder 19)
  - Joseph Katz (photos 297, 298) (Box 695, Folder 20)
  - photos from 1937 Poland trip (photos 299-309) (Box 695, Folder 21)
  - various photos taken at various dinners, speeches and function which Salo attended (photos 310-318) (Box 695, Folder 22)
  - Photo of former King Michael of Romania, various photos of dinners and talks attended by Salo, publicity photos of Salo, photo of Salo and Jeannette (photos 319-328) (Box 695, Folder 23)
  - Bruno Bernard negatives (Box 696, Folder 1)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 1-20) (Box 696, Folder 2)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 21-40) (Box 696, Folder 3)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 41-60) (Box 696, Folder 4)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 61-80) (Box 696, Folder 5)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 81-100) (Box 696, Folder 6)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 101-120) (Box 696, Folder 7)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 121-140) (Box 696, Folder 8)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 141-161) (Box 696, Folder 9)
  - Bruno Bernard "Beauty of Israel, Part 1: Girls" (photos 162-173) (Box 696, Folder 10)
  - Bruno Bernard "Israel: People and Places" (photos 174-194) (Box 696, Folder 11)
  - Bruno Bernard "Israel: People and Places" (photos 195-215) (Box 696, Folder 12)
  - Bruno Bernard "Israel: People and Places" (photos 216-234) (Box 696, Folder 13)
  - Bruno Bernard "Israel: People and Places" (photos 235-255) (Box 696, Folder 14)
  - Bruno Bernard "Israel: People and Places" (photos 256-270) (Box 696, Folder 15)
  - Salo's Abiturjenci Gimnazyum class (photo 1) (Box 697, Folder 1)
  - family photograph taken on the occasion of Estelle Katz' 50th anniversary (photo 2) (Box 697, Folder 2)
  - old school or club group photo (photo 3) (Box 697, Folder 3)
  - photos of a younger Salo Baron (photos 4-7) (Box 697, Folder 4)
  - publicity photos of Salo Baron (photos 8-12) (Box 697, Folder 5)
  - photo of the 35th anniversary celebration dinner for Zeta Beta Tau at Columbia University, 1939 and photos of Salo's 60th birthday Testimonial Dinner, 1955 (photos 13-15) (Box 697, Folder 6)
  - Salo in later years (photos 16, 17) (Box 697, Folder 7)
  - line drawing of Salo by Marvin Friedman, 19831983 (Box 698, Folder 1)
  - color drawing of Salo by Friedman, 19821982 (Box 698, Folder 2)
  - line drawing of the Barons overlooking papers on desk by Friedman, 19831983 (Box 698, Folder 3)
  - line drawing of the Barons at desk facing away by Friedman 1982 (Box 698, Folder 4)
  - another line drawing of the Barons at desk facing away1982 (Box 698, Folder 5)
  - color drawing of Mrs. Baron by Friedman 1982 (Box 698, Folder 6)
  - line drawing of the Baron Canaan, CT, house by Friedman 1982 (Box 698, Folder 7)
  - photo album for a reception at Columbia University for the "Baron Professorship" 5/2/79 (Box 699, Folder 1)
  - Great grandchildren 1980-84 (Box 700, Folder 1)
  - Great grandchildren 1983-85 (Box 700, Folder 2)
  - Great grandchildren 1984-88 (Box 700, Folder 3)
  - Gitelle family 19791979 (Box 700, Folder 4)
  - Gitelle family 1960-76 (Box 700, Folder 5)
  - Tobey Gitelle wedding (Box 700, Folder 6)
  - Tancer family wedding (Box 700, Folder 7)
  - Tancer family 1970's and 80's (Box 700, Folder 8)
  - Tancer family 1960`s and 70`s (Box 700, Folder 9)
  - Tancer family 1960`s and 70`s (Box 700, Folder 10)
  - Early Tancer family 1950`s and 60`s (Box 700, Folder 11)
  - Baron Group photos 1910`s - 1920's (Box 701, Folder 1)
  - AJAS Annual Meeting 19491949 (Box 701, Folder 2)
  - Israel speech (Box 701, Folder 3)
  - Midwest section of JSB 1950 (Box 701, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Fed. Comm. on Ed. 3/9/513/9/51 (Box 701, Folder 5)
  - Conference on Jewish Relations speech 12/8/5312/8/53 (Box 701, Folder 6)
  - Meeting JPS 10/30/6010/30/60 (Box 701, Folder 7)
  - N.Y. Event 1961 (Box 701, Folder 8)
  - Baron at Bryant University 1966 (Box 701, Folder 9)
  - B'nai B'rith lunch 2/692/69 (Box 701, Folder 10)
  - Dropsie University 1973 (Box 701, Folder 11)
  - Inauguration of Gerson Cohen 10/23/7310/23/73 (Box 701, Folder 12)
  - N.Y.U. 1973 (Box 701, Folder 13)
  - Kaplan Colloquium 12/7/8012/7/80 (Box 701, Folder 14)
  - Oxford-Yarnton Centre of Post-Graduate Hebrew Studies 5/26/835/26/83 (Box 701, Folder 15)
  - Hobart's William Smith Colleges 19861986 (Box 701, Folder 16)
  - Yeshiva University (Box 701, Folder 17)
  - Columbia University (Box 701, Folder 18)
  - Columbia University (Box 701, Folder 19)
  - Baron Prize in Jewish Studies 5/26/895/26/89 (Box 701, Folder 20)
  - University of Florida event (Box 701, Folder 21)
  - African Tour (Box 701, Folder 22)
  - Misc. events (Box 701, Folder 23)
  - Baron group photos 1950`s-1960`s (Box 701, Folder 24)
  - Unidentifiable event (Box 701, Folder 25)
  - American Friends of the Alliance Israelite Universelle; 19731973 (Box 701, Folder 26)
  - Jeanette Meisel childhood photos (1-8) (Box 702, Folder 1)
  - Young Jeanette Meisel (9-34) (Box 702, Folder 2)
  - Jeanette Baron (35-42) (Box 702, Folder 3)
  - Jeanette Baron photos in South Africa (43-52) (Box 702, Folder 4)
  - Jeanette Baron (53-76) (Box 702, Folder 5)
  - X-ray of Jeanette Baron's right thumb(77) (Box 702, Folder 6)
  - 1/16/75 accident site and Jeanette Baron (Box 702, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous photos of the Baron's (92-96) (Box 702, Folder 8)
  - 1975 photos of the Baron's (97-98) (Box 702, Folder 9)
  - later photos of the Baron's (99-101) (Box 702, Folder 10)
  - Salo Baron at Canaan homes 1975-87 (102-106) (Box 702, Folder 11)
  - Canaan library (107-126) (Box 702, Folder 12)
  - Baron's bust (127-128) (Box 702, Folder 13)
  - Early Baron Family photos (1-24) (Box 703, Folder 1)
  - Early Baron Family photos (25-48) (Box 703, Folder 2)
  - Baron Family photos (49-92) (Box 703, Folder 3)
  - Early Shoshana photos (93-110) (Box 703, Folder 4)
  - Early Shoshana photos (111-149) (Box 703, Folder 5)
  - Shoshana photos (150-166) (Box 703, Folder 6)
  - Shoshana events (167-171) (Box 703, Folder 7)
  - Early Tobey negatives and photos (172-197) (Box 703, Folder 8)
  - Tobey photos (198-209) (Box 703, Folder 9)
  - Baron's Lisbon Trip 1964 (210-214) (Box 703, Folder 10)
  - Salo and Jeanette 1944-1981 (215-235) (Box 703, Folder 11)
  - Young Baron (Box 704, Folder 1)
  - Baron pub photos (Box 704, Folder 2)
  - Baron pub photo; negatives (Box 704, Folder 3)
  - Morty (Box 704, Folder 4)
  - 2 photos of Jeanette Meisel Baron? (Box 704, Folder 5)
  - slides of Tel Aviv University (Box 704, Folder 6)
- Series 11. Audio-Visual Series, 5 linear ft. (10 boxes)
  This series contains mostly reel-to-reel tapes of Baron's lectures and speeches, as well as some audiotapes, videotapes and records. There is at least one videotaped interview of Baron by Zvi Ankori, a former student, in 1987.
  - Our Medieval Legacy (1956), part I; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 705, Folder 1)
  - Our Medieval Legacy (1956), part II; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 705, Folder 2)
  - Our Medieval Legacy (1956), part III; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 705, Folder 3)
  - Dynamics of Emancipation (1956), part I; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 705, Folder 4)
  - Dynamics of Emancipation (1956), part II; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 705, Folder 5)
  - Dynamics of Emancipation (1956), part III; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 705, Folder 6)
  - Israel in Antiquity and Today (1956); part I; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 705, Folder 7)
  - Israel in Antiquity and Today (1956); part II; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 705, Folder 8)
  - Israel in Antiquity and Today (1956); part III; magnetic tape(1956) (Box 706, Folder 1)
  - The European Jewish Community in Temple (?) Israel Century (?) 1854-1954; magnetic tape (1955) (Box 706, Folder 2)
  - The European Jewish Community in Temple (?) Israel Century (?) 1854-1954; magnetic tape (1955) (Box 706, Folder 3)
  - Friday Night Special I, WEVD (1973); magnetic tape(1973) (Box 706, Folder 4)
  - Friday Night Special II, WEVD (1973); magnetic tape(1973) (Box 706, Folder 5)
  - Point of View (11-20-77); magnetic tape (Box 706, Folder 6)
  - Point of View (11-27-77); magnetic tape (Box 706, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Address; magnetic tape (Box 707, Folder 1)
  - Liberalism I; magnetic tape (Box 707, Folder 2)
  - Liberalism II; magnetic tape (Box 707, Folder 3)
  - Liberalism I, II; magnetic tape (Box 707, Folder 4)
  - Magnetic tape, no title (Box 707, Folder 5)
  - Magnetic tape, no title (Box 707, Folder 6)
  - Magnetic tape, no title (Box 707, Folder 7)
  - Magnetic tape, no title (Box 708, Folder 1)
  - Magnetic tape from Israel Transcription Service (1958)(1958) (Box 708, Folder 2)
  - Liberalism I; magnetic tape (Box 708, Folder 3)
  - Liberalism II; magnetic tape (Box 708, Folder 4)
  - Interview Jan 1, 1954 with Estelle Sbinberger (?); magnetic tape (Box 708, Folder 5)
  - Books for American Jewry (1953); magnetic tape(1953) (Box 708, Folder 6)
  - Magnetic tape from Israel (1954) (Box 708, Folder 7)
  - Interview with Baron; 1, 2; Video tape (Box 709, Folder 1)
  - Interview with Baron; 3, 4; Video tape (Box 709, Folder 2)
  - Interview with Baron; 5, 6; Video tape (Box 709, Folder 3)
  - Interview with Baron; 1; Video tape (Box 709, Folder 4)
  - Interview with Baron; 2; Video tape (Box 709, Folder 5)
  - Interview with Baron; 3; Video tape (Box 709, Folder 6)
  - Hannah Arendt; An Intellectual Portrait; cassette (Box 710, Folder 1)
  - Steeled by Adversity; cassette (Box 710, Folder 2)
  - Overview of Modern Jewish History (1973); cassette(1973) (Box 710, Folder 3)
  - Overview of Modern Jewish History (1973); cassette(1973) (Box 710, Folder 4)
  - Henken, Glick; cassette (Box 711, Folder 1)
  - WEVD interview with J. Blau on Steeled by Adversity; cassette (Box 711, Folder 2)
  - The UJA Young Leadership Cabinet Lectures in Modern Jewish History (1973); cassette(1973) (Box 711, Folder 3)
  - Cassette; no title (Box 711, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Service, Philip E. Mosely (1972); cassette(1972) (Box 712, Folder 1)
  - Cassette; no title (Box 712, Folder 2)
  - Cassette; no title (Box 712, Folder 3)
  - Cassette; no title (Box 712, Folder 4)
  - Night Music Presents - Haganah, Songs of the Jewish Underground, records; Jewish Holiday Dances and Songs, records; Kindertotenlieder by Mahler, record; Shoshana Damari sings Israeli Favorites, record; The World of Sholem Aleichem, record; Living Spanish, a complete language course, record; S. Dzigan, Turistn in Israel, record; Recordings by Noah Nachbush, records; Palestine Dances and Songs, records (Box 713)
  - Jewish Teachers Association Irving Rosenblum; Pres. 33rd Annual Luncheon (1960); Adorah Award to S. W. Baron WNYC, record plus misc. papers (Box 714, Folder 1)
  - New World - A Coming Genocide, record (Box 714, Folder 2)
  - New World - A Coming Genocide, record (Box 714, Folder 3)
  - The Lord Is One, Chorus of the Israeli Temple of Milan, record (Box 714, Folder 4)
  - Mahler, Das Lied von der Erde; records (Box 714, Folder 5)